<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-11-13T06:25:56-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Running Uphill</title><subtitle>Life, code, and running uphill.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Life lately</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/life/2024/11/12/live-lately.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life lately" /><published>2024-11-12T16:25:24-05:00</published><updated>2024-11-12T16:25:24-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/life/2024/11/12/live-lately</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/life/2024/11/12/live-lately.html"><![CDATA[<p>I became a mom on Halloween in 2023, and then returned to work 3 months later to find myself completely changed. In May, I resigned to focus entirely on our baby.</p>

<p>My career over the past 11 years has made me so proud. A girl from the hills of West Virginia grows into an exceptional engineer at Twitter. It terrifies me to loose that.</p>

<p>It also terrifies me to miss out on the moments where I can take our 12 month old to the park at 3pm, fall leaves crunching beneath our feet, and become completely absorbed by his smile as I push him on the swing.</p>

<p>In my career and life, I have found power in choosing the difficult path. I refuse to believe my only choice at having a fulfilling career, is returning to a 40+ hour work week.</p>

<p>I’m not sure where I’m going yet. I have some ideas. All of it is mildly terrifying.</p>

<p>A couple of days ago, it dawned on me to start a blog. I’ve always wanted one - but feared opening myself up to judgement of others. As of May, I would still sweat a little whenever I open a pull request.</p>

<p>Being a stay-at-home-mom, has exposed me to the ultimate judgement. So what’s a few random thoughts on the internet going to hurt?</p>

<p>As a woman in tech, I have struggled with extreme imposter syndrome - never sure what I’m saying is true, always assuming someone else knows more. I think the act of putting my knowledge down on a page would help tremendously.</p>

<p>Stay tuned.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I became a mom on Halloween in 2023, and then returned to work 3 months later to find myself completely changed. In May, I resigned to focus entirely on our baby.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why running uphill?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/life/2024/11/12/running-uphill.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why running uphill?" /><published>2024-11-12T16:16:24-05:00</published><updated>2024-11-12T16:16:24-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/life/2024/11/12/running-uphill</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/life/2024/11/12/running-uphill.html"><![CDATA[<p>I think it is one of my greatest strengths. This past September I ran the Park’s Half Marathon, and there’s part of the trail called “The Shredder” - basically a steep incline at mile 11. I noticed when it came, I picked up my pace and leaned into the challenge - leaving everyone else behind me. I think I do this a lot in life, and it’s core to who I am.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="life" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it is one of my greatest strengths. This past September I ran the Park’s Half Marathon, and there’s part of the trail called “The Shredder” - basically a steep incline at mile 11. I noticed when it came, I picked up my pace and leaned into the challenge - leaving everyone else behind me. I think I do this a lot in life, and it’s core to who I am.]]></summary></entry></feed>